<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Data Science and GenAI on ArangoDB Documentation</title><link>http://localhost/3.13/data-science/</link><description>Recent content in Data Science and GenAI on ArangoDB Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://localhost/3.13/data-science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ArangoDB GraphML</title><link>http://localhost/3.13/data-science/graphml/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost/3.13/data-science/graphml/</guid><description>Traditional Machine Learning (ML) overlooks the connections and relationships between data points, which is where graph machine learning excels. However, accessibility to GraphML has been limited to sizable enterprises equipped with specialized teams of data scientists. ArangoDB simplifies the utilization of Graph Machine Learning, enabling a broader range of personas to extract profound insights from their data.
With ArangoDB, you can solve high-computational graph problems using Graph Machine Learning. Apply it on a selected graph to predict connections, get better product recommendations, classify nodes, and perform node embeddings.</description></item><item><title>Notebook Servers</title><link>http://localhost/3.13/data-science/notebook-servers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost/3.13/data-science/notebook-servers/</guid><description>ArangoDB Platform ArangoDB Notebooks provide a Python-based, Jupyter-compatible interface for building and experimenting with graph-powered data, GenAI, and graph machine learning workflows directly connected to ArangoDB databases. The notebook servers are embedded in the ArangoDB Platform ecosystem and offer a pre-configured environment where everything, including all the necessary services and configurations, comes preloaded. You don&amp;rsquo;t need to set up or configure the infrastructure, and can immediately start using the GraphML and GenAI functionalities.</description></item><item><title>Large Language Models (LLMs) and Knowledge Graphs</title><link>http://localhost/3.13/data-science/llm-knowledge-graphs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost/3.13/data-science/llm-knowledge-graphs/</guid><description>Large language models (LLMs) and knowledge graphs are two prominent and contrasting concepts, each possessing unique characteristics and functionalities that significantly impact the methods we employ to extract valuable insights from constantly expanding and complex datasets.
LLMs, exemplified by OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s ChatGPT, represent a class of powerful language transformers. These models leverage advanced neural networks to exhibit a remarkable proficiency in understanding, generating, and participating in contextually-aware conversations.
On the other hand, knowledge graphs contain carefully structured data and are designed to capture intricate relationships among discrete and seemingly unrelated information.</description></item><item><title>Adapters</title><link>http://localhost/3.13/data-science/adapters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost/3.13/data-science/adapters/</guid><description>ArangoDB Adapters provide a convenient way to integrate ArangoDB with popular data science tools. By enabling you to to use your preferred programming languages and libraries, these adapters simplify the data analysis process and make it easier to leverage the power of ArangoDB in data science.
Read more about the adapters available in ArangoDB:
NetworkX cuGraph PyTorch Geometric (PyG) Deep Graph Library (DGL) Resource Description Framework (RDF)</description></item></channel></rss>