<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Generative Artificial Intelligence (GenAI) and Data Science on ArangoDB Documentation</title><link>http://localhost/3.13/data-science/</link><description>Recent content in Generative Artificial Intelligence (GenAI) and Data Science on ArangoDB Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://localhost/3.13/data-science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>GraphRAG</title><link>http://localhost/3.13/data-science/graphrag/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost/3.13/data-science/graphrag/</guid><description>ArangoDB Platform The ArangoDB Platform &amp;amp; GenAI Suite is available as a pre-release. To get exclusive early access, get in touch&amp;nbsp; with the ArangoDB team. Introduction Large language models (LLMs) and knowledge graphs are two prominent and contrasting concepts, each possessing unique characteristics and functionalities that significantly impact the methods we employ to extract valuable insights from constantly expanding and complex datasets.
LLMs, such as those powering OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s ChatGPT, represent a class of powerful language transformers.</description></item><item><title>ArangoDB GraphML</title><link>http://localhost/3.13/data-science/graphml/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost/3.13/data-science/graphml/</guid><description>ArangoDB Platform The ArangoDB Platform &amp;amp; GenAI Suite is available as a pre-release. To get exclusive early access, get in touch&amp;nbsp; with the ArangoDB team. Traditional Machine Learning (ML) overlooks the connections and relationships between data points, which is where graph machine learning excels. However, accessibility to GraphML has been limited to sizable enterprises equipped with specialized teams of data scientists. ArangoDB simplifies the utilization of Graph Machine Learning, enabling a broader range of personas to extract profound insights from their data.</description></item><item><title>ArangoDB integrations for data science</title><link>http://localhost/3.13/data-science/integrations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost/3.13/data-science/integrations/</guid><description>ArangoDB Adapters provide a convenient way to integrate ArangoDB with popular data science tools. By enabling you to to use your preferred programming languages and libraries, these adapters simplify the data analysis process and make it easier to leverage the power of ArangoDB in data science.
Read more about the adapters available in ArangoDB:
NetworkX cuGraph PyTorch Geometric (PyG) Deep Graph Library (DGL) Resource Description Framework (RDF)</description></item><item><title>Notebook Servers</title><link>http://localhost/3.13/data-science/notebook-servers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost/3.13/data-science/notebook-servers/</guid><description>ArangoDB Platform The ArangoDB Platform &amp;amp; GenAI Suite is available as a pre-release. To get exclusive early access, get in touch&amp;nbsp; with the ArangoDB team. ArangoDB Notebooks provide a Python-based, Jupyter-compatible interface for building and experimenting with graph-powered data, GenAI, and graph machine learning workflows directly connected to ArangoDB databases. The notebook servers are embedded in the ArangoDB Platform ecosystem and offer a pre-configured environment where everything, including all the necessary services and configurations, comes preloaded.</description></item></channel></rss>