<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Features and Capabilities on ArangoDB Documentation</title><link>http://localhost/3.12/about-arangodb/features/</link><description>Recent content in Features and Capabilities on ArangoDB Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://localhost/3.12/about-arangodb/features/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Feature list of the ArangoDB core database system</title><link>http://localhost/3.12/about-arangodb/features/core/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost/3.12/about-arangodb/features/core/</guid><description>Feature parity between the Community Edition and the Enterprise Edition is available from v3.12.5 onward. General Graph Database: Native support for storing and querying graphs comprised of vertices and edges. You can model complex domains because edges are documents without any restrictions in complexity.
Document Database: A modern document database system that allows you to model data intuitively and evolve the data model easily. Documents can be organized in collections, and collections in databases for multi-tenancy.</description></item><item><title>Feature list of the ArangoDB Platform</title><link>http://localhost/3.12/about-arangodb/features/platform/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost/3.12/about-arangodb/features/platform/</guid><description>For in-depth information about the ArangoDB Platform as a whole and how to deploy and use it, see The ArangoDB Platform.
Architecture Core Database: The ArangoDB database system forms the solid core of the ArangoDB Platform.
Kubernetes: An open-source container orchestration system for automating software deployment, scaling, and management designed by Google. It is the autopilot for operating ArangoDB clusters and the additional Platform services.
Helm: A package manager for Kubernetes that enables consistent, repeatable installations and version control.</description></item><item><title>Highlights by Version</title><link>http://localhost/3.12/about-arangodb/features/highlights-by-version/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost/3.12/about-arangodb/features/highlights-by-version/</guid><description>Version 3.12 From version 3.12.5 onward, the prepackaged binaries and official Docker images of the Community Edition include all features of the Enterprise Edition. See ArangoDB Editions for details. All Editions
Improved memory accounting: Better tracking and observability of memory consumption for ArangoDB deployments and reduced memory usage.
wildcard Analyzer: Accelerate LIKE searches with _ and % wildcards against Views and inverted indexes with n-grams to quickly find candidate matches.</description></item></channel></rss>