<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ArangoDB GraphML on ArangoDB Documentation</title><link>http://localhost/3.12/data-science/graphml/</link><description>Recent content in ArangoDB GraphML on ArangoDB Documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://localhost/3.12/data-science/graphml/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to get started with GraphML</title><link>http://localhost/3.12/data-science/graphml/quickstart/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost/3.12/data-science/graphml/quickstart/</guid><description>ArangoDB Platform Web interface versus Jupyter Notebooks The ArangoDB Platform provides enterprise-ready Graph Machine Learning in two options, tailored to suit diverse requirements and preferences:
Using the web interface In a scriptable manner, using the integrated Jupyter Notebooks and the HTTP API for GraphML Setup Web Interface Notebooks The web interface of the ArangoDB Platform allows you to create, configure, and run a full machine learning workflow for GraphML. To get started, see the Web interface for GraphML page.</description></item><item><title>How to use GraphML in the ArangoDB Platform web interface</title><link>http://localhost/3.12/data-science/graphml/ui/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost/3.12/data-science/graphml/ui/</guid><description>ArangoDB Platform The GraphML workflow in the web interface The entire process is organized into sequential steps within a Project, giving you a clear path from data to prediction:
Featurization: Select your data and convert it into numerical representations. Training: Train a GraphSAGE model on the features and graph structure. Model Selection: Evaluate the trained models and choose the best one. Prediction: Use the selected model to generate predictions on your data.</description></item><item><title>How to use GraphML in a scriptable manner</title><link>http://localhost/3.12/data-science/graphml/notebooks-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost/3.12/data-science/graphml/notebooks-api/</guid><description>ArangoDB Platform The ArangoDB Platform provides an easy-to-use &amp;amp; scalable interface to run Graph Machine Learning on ArangoDB data. Since all the orchestration and Machine Learning logic is managed by ArangoDB, all that is typically required are JSON specifications outlining individual processes to solve a Machine Learning task.
The arangoml Python package allows you to manage all the necessary GraphML components, including:
Project Management: Projects are a metadata-tracking entity that sit at the top level of ArangoDB GraphML.</description></item></channel></rss>